Guide to the Neal Lane papers, 1998-2001, MS 502 MS 502
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Audio/Visual, 1984-2002
  - A, September 20, 1996 (Box 88)
  - National Science Board Awards Dinner, May 7, 1997 (Box 88)
  - The 29th Annual Holiday Lecture by Professor Bassam Z. Shakhashiri - "Once Upon a Christmas Cheery in the Lab of Shakhashiri", 1998 (Box 88)
  - Food Safety Council Press Conference - C-SPAN2, August 25, 1998 (Box 88)
  - Mentoring Awards Event, September 10, 1998 (Box 88)
  - "Techno-Politics" - Ehlers Study, September 12, 1998 (Box 88)
  - Memorial Service for Congressman George E. Brown, Jr. - US Capitol, Statuary Hall, July 30, 1999 (Box 88)
  - National Science Foundation - 50th Anniversary Vignettes, November 1999 (Box 88)
  - Graduation - The Queen's University of Belfast, July 2000 (Box 88)
  - CITI - DH McMurtry, April 2, 2002 (Box 88)
  - "Escape From Mung Island" (Box 88)
  - Close-up Mars (Box 88)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory (Box 88)
  - "The Aurora Explained" (Box 88)
  - Neal Lane - CSPAN (Box 88)
  - "Card Trick" (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 1. Bernard Bailyn, The Living Past - Commitments for the Future (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 2. Stephen Hawking, Imagination and Change - Science in the Next Millenium (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 3. Poets Laureate, The American Voice in Poetry (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 4. Jazz: An Expression of Democracy (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 5. Professors Natalie Zemon Davis and Martin Marty, The Meaning of the Millenium (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 6. Women as Citizens: Vital Voices Through the Century (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 7. Professor Elie Wiesel, The Perils of Indifference: Lessons From a Violent Century (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 8. Dr. Vinton Cerf and Dr. Eric Lander, Informatics Meets Genomics (Box 88)
  - Millenium Evenings at the White House: 9. Dr. Marcia McNutt and Dr. Neil de Grasse Tyson, Exploration: Under the Sea, Beyond the Stars (Box 88)
  - Antarctica, December 1993 (Box 89)
  - Live...From Other Worlds: "To Mars Via Anarctica," "Student Drivers...Robot Divers.", December 3, 1993 (Box 89)
  - CRO Presentation Tape (Revised), December 3, 1993 (Box 89)
  - "Red Dog Mine - Alaska", March 2, 1994 (Box 89)
  - Live from Antarctica, December 1994 (Box 89)
  - Crystal Laboratory - PBS, June 7, 1995 (Box 89)
  - National Science Foundation - "Working in Antarctica: McMurdo, South Pole, Field Camps", August 1995 (Box 89)
  - National Science Foundation - "Responsible for a Continent: Managing Your Waste in Antarctica", November 7, 1995 (Box 89)
  - Nova - "Einstein Revealed", October 1, 1996 (Box 89)
  - AAAS Meeting - National Science Foundation, February 13, 1998 (Box 89)
  - White House Swearing In Ceremony for Neal Lane, Director, Office of Science and Technology Policy and Rita Colwell, Director, National Science Foundation, November 23, 1998 (Box 89)
  - Near Earth Asteroid Rendezvous (NEAR) - The Journey Continues, 1999 Update, March 15, 1999 (Box 89)
  - The 1999 National Science and Technology Medals Laureates, March 13, 2000 (Box 89)
  - 1999 National Medals of Science and Technology White House Ceremony, March 14, 2000 (Box 89)
  - March 7, 2000 NEAR Flyover 1 and 2 (Eros Rotation), March 14, 2000 (Box 89)
  - Live From Antarctica - "The Coldest, Windiest, Iciest Place on Earth" (Box 89)
  - Live From Antarctica - "From Pole to Planet" (Box 89)
  - Live From Antarctica - "Spaceship Southpole" (Box 89)
  - Live From Antarctica, Life in Antarctica - "Spaceship Southpole" (Box 89)
  - Live From Antarctica, Life in Antarctica - "Then and Now" (Box 89)
  - Red Dog Anthology: "Red Dog: The Beginning," "Red Dog: Season of Challenge," "The Future is Now," "Red Dog: The Bold Promise" (Box 89)
  - "The Journey" - North Slope Borough School District TV Studio (Box 89)
  - Introduction to NSF, NSF Proposal Review, NSF Budget Process, S and T Government: A Crisis of Purpose? (Box 89)
  - NSF Orientation Videos (Box 89)
  - The Baker Institute for Public Policy - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society: The Relationship Between Policy and Research in National Laboratories, Universities, Government, and Industry, November 1-2, 2003 (Box 89)
    booklet
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 1: Welcome and Introduction/Session 2: Energy, Environment and Security, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
    DVD video
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 3: Energy and Environment Science Panel, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 4: Energy and Environment Technology Panel, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 5: Nuclear Energy and Security, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 6: Nuclear Energy and Security Panel, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 7: Science and Technology Policy, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 8: Science and Technology Policy Advice in Government, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Djerejian Remarks/Session 9: Education and Technical Workforce, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 10: Education and Technical Workforce Panel, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 11: International Cooperation, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
  - Bridging the Gap Between Science and Society - Session 12: International Cooperation Panel, November 1, 2003 (Box 89)
- Series V: Baker Institute for Public Policy, work on outside boards, 2000-2011; 161071
  - CRDF: Retreat, 2003 - 2005; 161464 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Efficiency & Renewables Advisory Committee (ERAC), 2010 - 2011; 161466 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Federation of American Scientists (FAS), 2007 - 2009; 161481 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Federation of American Scientists (FAS), 2010; 161482 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Federation of American Scientists (FAS), 2010 - 2011; 161483 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Federation of American Scientists (FAS): Public Interest report, 2010 - 2011; 161484 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Fermi Lab: Director search, 2004; 161485 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Fermi Research Alliance (FRA), 2007 - 2008; 161486 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Fermi Research Alliance (FRA), 2009; 161487 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Fermi Research Alliance (FRA), 2010; 161488 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Harrington Board, 2005 - 2007; 161489 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Innovations, 2006; 161490 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Institute of Molecular Medicine (IMM): Scientific Advisory Board (UT-Health Science Center at Houston), 2004; 161491 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Kavli Institute for Theoretical Physics (KITP), 2004; 161492 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Kavli Institute for Theoretical Physics (KITP), 2005; 161493 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Kavli Institute for Theoretical Physics (KITP), 2006; 161494 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory Theoretical Division, 2001 - 2003; 161495 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory Theoretical Division, May 2003; 161496 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory Theoretical Division, 2005 - 2006; 161497 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory UT Austin proposal, 2004 - 2005; 161498 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research (NCAR), 2002; 161499 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF): National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA), 2000 - 2003; 161500 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF): NAPA Panel, 2001 - 2003; 161501 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - President's Council of Advisors on Science and Technology (PCAST) STEM - Higher education study, 2011; 161515 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - PCAST STEM - Undergraduate education, 2011; 161516 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - STEM Education - background, 2010 - 2011; 161518 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Sci Fi Visions, 2006 - 2007; 161519 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Sigma Xi Postdoc Survey, 2002; 161520 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists (UCS), 2002 - 2003; 161521 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists (UCS) - Scientific Integrity Articles, 2003 - 2004; 161522 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR), 2004; 161525 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR), 2005 - 2006; 161526 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR), February 2007; 161527 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR), May 2007; 161528 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR) publications, 2007; 161529 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Woodrow Wilson Center project, 2010 - 2011; 161545 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Images, powerpoints, documents (CDs), 2002 - 2004; 161546 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Series V: Addendum
  - The National Academies: National Research Council Committees
    - Committee for the Transportation of Radioactive Waste (CTRW)
      - Transportation of Hazardous Waste Study, 1969 (Box 91a, Folder 1)
      - Transportation of Hazardous Waste Study, 1983 (Box 91a, Folder 2)
      - Association of American Railroads: Reports on Transporting Nuclear Waste, 1998 (Box 91a, Folder 3)
      - Committee Brochures, undated (Box 91a, Folder 4)
      - Department of Energy Transportation Reports, 2002 (Box 91a, Folder 5)
      - Yucca Mountain Project, 5/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 6)
      - Meeting, 5/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 7)
      - Meeting, Agenda Book, 5/16-17/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 8)
      - Meeting, Agenda Book, 5/16-17/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 9)
      - Meeting, 7/24-26/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 10)
      - Meeting Notes, 7/25/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 11)
      - Meeting, 8/20/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 12)
      - Meetings, 10/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 13)
      - Meeting 3 Talking Points, 10/28/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 14)
      - Meeting 3, 10/30-31/2003 (Box 91a, Folder 15)
      - Materials and Correspondence, 2003 (Box 91a, Folder 16)
      - Chicago, 2/2-4/2004 (Box 91a, Folder 17)
      - Chicago, 2/2-4/2004 (Box 91a, Folder 18)
      - Chicago, Omnibus Questions, 2/3/2004 (Box 91a, Folder 19)
      - Chicago, Risk Perception / Communication, 2/3/2004 (Box 91a, Folder 20)
      - Chicago, 2/3/2004 (Box 91a, Folder 21)
      - Chicago Trip, 2/3-4/2004 (Box 91a, Folder 22)
      - DC Meeting, 5/5-6/2004 (Box 91a, Folder 23)
      - Meeting, DC, 5/5/2004-5/6/2004 (Box 91b, Folder 1)
      - Meeting, DC, 5/5/2004-5/6/2004 (Box 91b, Folder 2)
      - Meeting, DC, 5/5/2004-5/6/2004 (Box 91b, Folder 3)
      - Meeting, DC, 5/5/2004-5/6/2004 (Box 91b, Folder 4)
      - ALB Meeting, Handouts, 7/21/2004-7/23/2004 (Box 91b, Folder 5)
      - DC Meeting, 11/3/2004-5/20/2004 (Box 91b, Folder 6)
      - Transportation of Radioactive Waste, Principal Findings and Recommendations, 2004 (Box 91b, Folder 7)
      - Transportation of Radioactive Waste, Principal Findings and Recommendations, 2004 (Box 91b, Folder 8)
      - Meeting: Albuquerque to DC, 2004-2005 (Box 91b, Folder 9)
      - DC (Last Meeting), 7/18/2005-7/20/2005 (Box 91b, Folder 10)
      - Keck Center of the National Academes, 12/1/2004 (Box 91b, Folder 11)
    - Elementary Particle Physics (EPP)
      - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 1/31/2005-2/1/2005 (Box 91b, Folder 12)
      - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory, 5/16/2005-5/17/2005 (Box 91b, Folder 13)
      - Shapiro Committee, Meeting 1, 11/30-12/1/2005 (Box 91b, Folder 14)
      - Shapiro Committee, Meeting 1, 11/30-12/1/2005 (Box 91b, Folder 15)
      - Conference Calls and Final Meeting, 2006 (Box 91b, Folder 16)
    - Earth Service and Applications from Space
      - Earth Service and Applications from Space Meeting, 1/5-6/2005 (Box 91b, Folder 17)
      - Earth Service and Applications from Space, 2005-2007 (Box 91b, Folder 18)
      - Earth Service and Applications from Space, 2005-2007 (Box 91b, Folder 19)
    - Data Integrity Committee
      - 1st Meeting, 4/16-17/2007 (Box 91b, Folder 20)
      - Background Book, 2/2007 (Box 91b, Folder 21)
      - Meeting, 9/17-18/2007 (Box 91b, Folder 22)
      - Data Integrity Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 91b, Folder 23)
      - Data Integrity Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 91b, Folder 24)
      - Data Integrity Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 91c, Folder 1)
    - Keck Foundation
      - Keck Five Year Review Panel, Panel Conference Call, 2007/7/23 (Box 91c, Folder 2)
      - Keck Futures: Five Year Review Panel Reports (Draft), 2008/2 (Box 91c, Folder 3)
      - Keck Foundation Review, 2010/2 (Box 91c, Folder 4)
      - Keck Foundation: Program Evaluation (Supplemental Materials), 2008 (Box 91c, Folder 5)
      - Keck Foundation: Program Evaluation, 2010/6/29 (Box 91c, Folder 6)
    - National Weather Service Review
      - National Weather Service Review, 2012 (Box 91c, Folder 8)
      - National Weather Service Review, 2012 (Box 91c, Folder 7)
    - Policy and Global Affairs Division (PGA)
      - PGA Committee, 2005 (Box 91c, Folder 9)
      - PGA Review, 2013 (Box 91c, Folder 10)
      - PGA Review, 2013 (Box 91c, Folder 11)
      - PGA Triennial Reports, 2013/11 (Box 91c, Folder 12)
    - PGA: Committee on Science, Engineering, and Public Policy
      - Committee on Science and Technology in the National Interest: Meeting, 2008/4/21 (Box 91c, Folder 16)
      - Federal S & T Committee Appointments, 2003 (Box 91c, Folder 13)
      - S & T Committee Appointments, 2003 (Box 91c, Folder 14)
      - COSEPUP Unit Review, 2006/3 (Box 91c, Folder 15)
  - American Academy of Arts and Science
    - Council and Executive Committee for the Council
      - Fellows Reception, 9/16/2013 (Box 91c, Folder 17)
      - Inducion, 10/2004 (Box 91c, Folder 18)
      - Induction, 10/2004 (Box 91c, Folder 19)
      - Bulletin: Annual Report, 2004 (Box 91c, Folder 20)
      - Rules in Space Workshop, 3/4/2005 (Box 91c, Folder 21)
      - Press Clippings, 6/2004-4/11/2005 (Box 91c, Folder 22)
      - Celebration 225th Anniversary, Lane's Speech, 4/21/2005 (Box 91c, Folder 23)
      - Induction, 2005 (Box 91c, Folder 24)
      - Unnamed File, 2005 (Box 91c, Folder 25)
      - Council and CISS, 2006 (Box 91c, Folder 26)
      - Press Clippings, 10/2006-4/2007 (Box 91d, Folder 1)
      - Meetings and Correspondence, 3/2007-4/2007 (Box 91d, Folder 2)
      - Executive Committee of the Council Teleconference Meeting, 8/14/2007 (Box 91d, Folder 3)
      - Induction, 10/2007 (Box 91d, Folder 4)
      - Committee for International Security Studies, 2007 (Box 91d, Folder 5)
      - Induction, 10/11-12/2008 (Box 91d, Folder 6)
      - Induction, 0/11-12/2008 (Box 91d, Folder 7)
      - Fellowship Programs, 2009 (Box 91d, Folder 8)
      - Selected Media Coverage, 4/2009-10/2009 (Box 91d, Folder 9)
      - Induction, 10/2009 (Box 91d, Folder 10)
      - Highlights, 10/2009 (Box 91d, Folder 11)
      - Induction, 10/2009 (Box 91d, Folder 12)
      - Global Nuclear Future Policy Briefing, 10/10/2009 (Box 91d, Folder 13)
      - Humanities Planning Group, 11/19/2009-11/20/2009 (Box 91d, Folder 14)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 2/5/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 15)
      - Council Meeting, 4/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 16)
      - Meeting Talking Points, 2010 (Box 91d, Folder 17)
      - Supplemental Committee Reports, 4/16/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 18)
      - Meeting of Trust, 4/16/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 19)
      - Council and Trust Joint Meeting, 4/16/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 20)
      - Interim Executive Committee, 4/16/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 21)
      - Studies and Publications Committees, 9/8/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 22)
      - Introducing the Humanities Indicators, 2010 (Box 91d, Folder 23)
      - Celebrating the Arts and the Humanities, 10/8/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 24)
      - Induction Programs, 10/8/2010-10/10/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 25)
      - Meeting Executive Board Committee, 10/9/2010 (Box 91d, Folder 26)
      - Meetings- Induction Celebration, Undated (Box 91d, Folder 27)
      - Meeting of the Committee Officers and Directors, 1/31/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 28)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 3/16/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 29)
      - Council Meeting, 4/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 30)
      - Fellows, 4/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 31)
      - Overview of Programs and Publications, 4/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 32)
      - Financial Highlights, Undated (Box 91d, Folder 33)
      - Joint Meeting Council and Trust, 4/15/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 34)
      - Trust Meeting, 4/15/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 35)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 6/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 36)
      - Press Clippings, 4/1/2011-9/7/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 37)
      - Executive Committee, 9/30/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 38)
      - Council Meeting, 9/30/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 39)
      - Trust Meeting, 9/30/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 40)
      - Joint Meeting of Council and Trust, 9/30/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 41)
      - Celebrating the Arts, 9/30/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 42)
      - Induction Programs, 10/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 43)
      - Council Meeting, 4/14/2011-4/15/2011 (Box 91d, Folder 44)
      - Induction Programs, 2011 (Box 91d, Folder 45)
      - Induction, Council, Etc., 2011-2012 (Box 91d, Folder 46)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, 1/18/2012 (Box 91d, Folder 47)
      - Executive Committee, 2/14/2012 (Box 91d, Folder 48)
      - Council Meeting, 4/12/2012 (Box 91d, Folder 49)
      - Joint Meeting, Council and Trust, 4/13/2012 (Box 91d, Folder 50)
      - Trust Meeting, 4/13/2012 (Box 91d, Folder 51)
      - Induction, 10/2012 (Box 91e, Folder 1)
      - Board and Orientation Induction, 10/2012 (Box 91e, Folder 2)
      - Meeting of the Executive, 10/6/2012 (Box 91e, Folder 3)
      - Executive Committee, 11/2012-12/2012 (Box 91e, Folder 4)
      - Executive Meeting, 1/15/2016 (Box 91e, Folder 5)
      - Publications and Studies Committee Meeting, 1/24/2013 (Box 91e, Folder 6)
      - Council, etc., 4/2013 (Box 91e, Folder 7)
      - Induction, 10/2013 (Box 91e, Folder 8)
      - Executive Committee, 4/12/2014 (Box 91e, Folder 9)
    - Committee for International Security Studies
      - Committee on International Security Studies, 2001 (Box 91e, Folder 10)
      - Committee on International Security Studies, 8/2001 (Box 91e, Folder 11)
      - Committee on International Security Studies, 8/9/2001-8/10/2001 (Box 91e, Folder 12)
      - Committee on International Security Studies, 2/2002 (Box 91e, Folder 13)
      - Committee on International Security Studies, 4/11/2003 (Box 91e, Folder 14)
      - Committee on International Security Studies, 2002-2005 (Box 91e, Folder 15)
      - Committee on International Security Studies: Space Policy, 2002-2004 (Box 91e, Folder 16)
      - Committee on International Security Studies, 4/30/2004 (Box 91e, Folder 17)
    - ARISE
      - ARISE I, 2007 (Box 91e, Folder 18)
      - ARISE Call, 9/28/2010 (Box 91e, Folder 19)
      - ARISE Committee, 3/4/2011 (Box 91e, Folder 20)
      - ARISE II Committee, 3/18/2011 (Box 91e, Folder 21)
      - ARISE II DC Meeting, 3/24/2011 (Box 91e, Folder 22)
      - ARISE II Lounsbery, 10/2011 (Box 91e, Folder 23)
      - ARISE II Edits, 2012 (Box 91e, Folder 24)
      - ARISE II Meeting Materials, Undated (Box 91e, Folder 25)
    - Initiative for Science, Technology, and Engineering: Oversight Committee
      - Initiative for Science and Technology, "Vest Committee", 2006 (Box 91e, Folder 26)
      - Initiative for Sci, Tech, Engin, 7/3/2008 (Box 91e, Folder 27)
      - Initiative for Sci + Tech, "Vest Committee", 2012 (Box 91e, Folder 28)
  - Federal Research and Development Funding Materials
    - Federal R+D Funding Materials, 2000-2001 (Box 91f, Folder 1)
    - Federal R+D Funding Materials, 2001-2002 (Box 91f, Folder 2)
    - Federal R+D Budgets, FY 2002-2002 (Box 91f, Folder 3)
    - NSF Current Plan, FY 2002 (Box 91f, Folder 4)
    - Federal R+D Funding, Pre-2003 (Box 91f, Folder 5)
    - Federal R+D Budgets, FY 2003-2004 (Box 91f, Folder 6)
    - S&T Workforce- Science and Engineering Higher Education, 2003-2004 (Box 91f, Folder 7)
    - Federal R+D Budget, FY 2004 (Box 91f, Folder 8)
    - Federal R+D Budgets, FY 2005 (Box 91f, Folder 9)
    - Federal R+D Request, FY 2006 (Box 91f, Folder 10)
    - Budget, FY 2006 (Box 91f, Folder 11)
    - R&D Request to Congress, FY 2007 (Box 91f, Folder 12)
    - AAAS, R+D Budgetsm, FY 2008 (Box 91f, Folder 13)
  - Indigent Care Task Force (ICTF) Texas
    - "Solving DFW's Biggest Problem", 2004 (Box 91f, Folder 14)
    - Access to Healthcare in Texas- Index of Reference, 2005 (Box 91f, Folder 15)
    - "Changes in Economic Conditions and Health Insurance Coverage, 2005 (Box 91f, Folder 16)
    - Materials, 2005 (Box 91f, Folder 17)
    - Reports on Medicaid and Public Health, 2005 (Box 91f, Folder 18)
    - Events, 4/13/2006-4/17/2006 (Box 91f, Folder 19)
    - "Code Red" Annotated, 4/2006 (Box 91f, Folder 20)
    - "Code Red" Workshop, Austin, 8/25/2006 (Box 91f, Folder 21)
    - "Code Red" Final Report, 9/7/2006 (Box 91f, Folder 22)
    - "Code Red" Final Report, Undated (Box 91f, Folder 23)
    - "Code Red" Summary, Undated (Box 91f, Folder 24)
    - Greater San Antonio Chamber of Commerce Healthcare Summit, 9/7/2006 (Box 91f, Folder 25)
    - Dallas, 11/16/2007-11/17/2007 (Box 91f, Folder 26)
    - Workers' Cooperative, Inc., 2007 (Box 91g, Folder 1)
    - Texas Medical Association, Healthy Vision, 2010 (Box 91g, Folder 2)
    - "Code Red" Task Force Austin, 2/14/2012 (Box 91g, Folder 3)
  - Science and Technology Advisory Group, Taiwan
    - 23rd Board Meeting, Reference Materials, 12/2-6/2002 (Box 91g, Folder 4)
    - STAG Presentations, 11/2002 (Box 91g, Folder 5)
    - Science Materials, 2002 (Box 91g, Folder 6)
    - STAG Taiwan, 12/2002 (Box 91g, Folder 7)
    - STAG Taiwan, 12/2002 (Box 91g, Folder 8)
    - STAG Taiwan, 4/2006 (Box 91g, Folder 9)
    - STAG Taiwan, 2007 (Box 91g, Folder 10)
    - STAG Board, Taiwan, 11/16-20/2008 (Box 91g, Folder 11)
    - STAG Board, Taiwan, 11/2-6/2009 (Box 91g, Folder 12)
    - Taiwan NCK University, Undated (Box 91g, Folder 13)
  - Union of Concerned Scientist, Scientific Integrity
    - UCS, Science Integrity, Undated (Box 91g, Folder 14)
    - AAAS, UCS, Bush Science, Recent Federal Policy, 4/2004 (Box 91g, Folder 15)
    - AAAS, UCS, Bush Science, 2004 (Box 91g, Folder 16)
    - AAAS, UCS, Bush Science, 2004 (Box 91g, Folder 17)
    - AAAS, UCS, Bush Science, Waxman Report, 2003 (Box 91g, Folder 18)
  - Kavli Foundation
    - Report to the Kavli Foundation Board, 2007 (Box 91g, Folder 19)
    - Ten Year Review, Committee Meeting, 7/20-22/2011 (Box 91g, Folder 20)
    - Ten Year Review, Committee Meeting, 7/20-22/2011 (Box 91g, Folder 21)
  - Academy of Medicine Engineering and Science of Texas
    - Academy of Medicine, Engineering and Science of Texas, Conference, 2009 (Box 91g, Folder 22)
    - Conference, 1/5-6/2006 (Box 91h, Folder 1)
  - Toyota Technological Institute and Chicago
    - Materials, 2006-2012 (Box 91h, Folder 2)
    - Spring Board Meeting, 4/22/2013 (Box 91h, Folder 3)
  - Program of US-China Cooperation in Science Policy, Research, and Education
    - Materials, 2006-2007 (Box 91h, Folder 4)
    - Renewable Energy, 2008 (Box 91h, Folder 5)
  - China Foundation for Promotion of Education and Culture, Taiwan, 2007-2011
    - Taiwan, 2007-2011 (Box 91h, Folder 6)
  - Department of Energy: Efficiency and Renewables Advisory Committee (ERAC)
    - Advisory Committee, undated (Box 91h, Folder 7)
- Series VI: Science & Technology (S & T) Conference, 2003; 161547
  - S & T Conference programs, 2003; 161548 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - S & T Conference A List Invitations, 2003; 161549 (Box 91, Folder 16)